

Kyle Wagner

Marketing Manager & Visual Designer

ABOUT ----

Luang Prabang, Laos +856 2098044162 kylewag@me.com 1991-11-22

EDUCATION -

MA Geography
York University, Toronto

BA International Studies DePaul University, Chicago

SOCIAL -

in kyledwagner

★ t.me/kdwagner

O kyledwagner

\$\infty\$ +66 80 362 0972

LANGUAGES -

English

Japanese

Lao

• • • • •

• • • • •

D O O O

SUMMARY

Marketing and communications manager, digital designer and content creator with over four years of experience working with DMCs, Hotels, and NGOs. Creative, analytical and collaborative with international teams. Proficient in web design, branding, content writing, campaigns, and email marketing.

EXPERTISE -

Photoshop	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Sketch	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Illustrator	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ	HTML/CSS	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
InDesign	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Javascript	•0000
Adobe XD	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$		

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE -

Marketing Manager @ Focus Asia December 2017 -

Luang Prabang, Laos

- Created, executed and optimized email marketing strategy with 2x weekly send rate; yielded ~20% OR with ~5% CTR.
- Lead marketing team to redesign and rewrite 250pg travel catalogue for increased ROI.
- Rebranded luxury travel sub-brand including website development, logotype design and all marketing collaterals.
- Produced 'Asia On Stage' booth concept for ITB 2019 with single-page microsite, branding and print media.

Web Designer & Developer @ TYPE-C July 2018 -

Remote

- Programmed 2 microsites and designed social media ads for a campaign promoting Laos to the Singaporean market.
- Designed and coded three websites using the SquareSpace platform for clients in Singapore.
- Designed a postcard concept for a video production company in Toronto.

Project Cordinator @ GIZ July 2016 - April 2019

Luang Prabang, Laos

- Managed, conceptualized and designed presentations and A3 posters together with UNESCO office for heritage protection.
- Developed and designed booth layout for ITB Asia in Singapore for 2 years.
- Built a sustainable trade show booth for Paksé Ecotourim Forum.

Marketing Cordinator @ Tiger Trail Travel September 2014 - September 2017

Luang Prabang, Laos

- Redesigned visual communication platform including print-based signage, tour catalogues, brochures, logos, posters, business cards, and newsletters.
- Developed and produced original content for two responsive brand websites: Fairtrek.org and Biking-Laos.com.
- Conceptualized and executed an effective marketing plan, social media strategy, and brand presentation.